Did you ignore
your check-engine light?
(Penny:)No, Mr. Smarty-pants.
I ignored the fill-gas-tank light.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, Penny wants to exploit
any feelings you have for her...
(Sheldon:)...in order to get a ride to work.
Oh, uh, sure, let me just put this
in a travel mug.
-Hello?
-Hi.
(Penny:)Oh, Penny, this is Dr. Plimpton,
a leading expert on quantum cosmology.
(Penny:)Dr. Plimpton, Penny is a waitress
who doesn't understand...
(Penny:)...the role gasoline plays
in the internal combustion engine.
(Leonard:)-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you too.
(Penny:)-Are you enjoying your stay?
-Yes, very much.
(Sheldon:)Good.
(Sheldon:)Wonderful. Meaningless
pleasantries accomplished.
(Sheldon:)Elizabeth, Leonard's bathroom time
is coming up...
(Sheldon:)...and, believe me,
you do not want to follow him.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Leonard:)Okay, well, I guess I should get dressed
so I can take everyone to work.
(Leonard:)You and Sheldon and Sheldon's friend,
Dr. Plimpton, who you just met.